yifymoviesubtitles.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy - Yify Movie Subtitles For all Languages

## PRIVACY POLICY

## This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Releasedateusa.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://yifymoviesubtitles.com (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by YIFY Movie Subtitles.

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

### Doubleclick DART Coookie

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include

Google

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on ReleasedateUSA send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings.

Google Analytics

At releasedateusa.com we use third party services like Google Analytics to keep track of how many visitors visited our website. We do not store any of your personal information.

Some of the cookies stored by Google Analytics are:

_utma, _utmb, _utmc, _utmz, _utmv.

How we use collected information

yifymoviesubtitles.com may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

– To improve our Site

We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Changes to this privacy policy

Releasedateusa.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
